Office of Educational Affairs, School of Medicine Records UA146
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Syllabi, 1985 -- 2020; 1989 -- 2014; UA146.001; 36.0 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s) 18 digital objects containing 192 files.; 3.33 Gigabytes Of the 18 digital objects in this series, 13 have extent information and comprise 4.37 GBs of data.
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II, 1998, UA146.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus unit B Section I, 1998, UA146.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section II, 1998, UA146.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 1999, First Year, UA146.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Gastrointestinal Pathology Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Pathophysiology Gastrointestinal Syllabus Infectious Diseases, 2002, UA146.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Pathophysiology GI Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Pathophysiology Renal Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Behavioral Science Syllabus Part II, 1998, UA146.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Biochemistry Conferences, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Cardiovascular System Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Cell and Tissue Biology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Cell and Tissue Biology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Gastrointestinal tract Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - GI Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Gross Anatomy Thorax Syllabus, 2001, UA146.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Hematology Syllabus, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Human Growth and Development Syllabus, 2003, First Year, UA146.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 1993, First Year, UA146.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 1994, First Year, UA146.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Extremities Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Medical gross Anatomy Pelvis and Perineum Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part I of II, 2003, UA146.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part II of II, 2003, UA146.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Pathology Reproductive System Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Pathophysiology Renal Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II, 1997, UA146.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine Behavioral Science Part II Human Growth and Development, 2001, UA146.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine Nutrition and Medicine Basic Nutrition Block Syllabus, 2001, UA146.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine Program Syllabus, 2001, UA146.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Pulmonary Pathology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Pulmonary Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Renal Pathology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Renal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus unit B Section I, 1997, UA146.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Behavioral Science and Primary Care Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Biochemistry Conference, 1997, First Year, UA146.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 1997, First Year, UA146.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Cardiovascular System Pathology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Cell, Developmental and Tissue Biology Syllabus Histology Part I, 1993, UA146.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1998 First Year Fall Semester, 1998, First Year, UA146.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1998 First Year Spring Semester, 1998, First Year, UA146.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1998 Second Year Fall Semester, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1998 Second Year Spring Semester, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1998 Second Year Spring Semester, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Endocrine Pathology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Endocrine Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Epidemiology and Biostatistics Syllabus, 1993, UA146.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Epidemiology and Biostatistics Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Gross Anatomy Thorax Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Head Neck Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Histology Part I Lab Manuel, 1993, UA146.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - History of Medicine Syllabus, 1993, UA146.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Infectious Diarrhea PowerPoint, 1993, UA146.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Abdomen Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Medical Histology Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory Part I, 1997, UA146.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part II, 1998, UA146.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manuel, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 1994, First Year, UA146.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section III, 1996, UA146.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section II, 1997, UA146.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Hematology Syllabus, 2003, First Year, UA146.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Pathophysiology Cardiovascular Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Pathophysiology Reproductive Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Behavioral Science and Primary Care Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Behavioral Science; Part II Human Growth and Development, 1998, UA146.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 1998, First Year, UA146.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Call and Tissue Biology Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Cardiovascular System Pathology Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Cell, Tissue, and organ Biology Syllabus Part II, 2003, First Year, UA146.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Combined Cases Introduction, 2003, UA146.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Infectious Disease Cardiovascular Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Infectious Diseases Pulmonary Section Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Introduction to Clinical Skills Syllabus, 2003, UA146.001.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Head and Neck Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory Part I, 1997, UA146.001.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manuel, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 1994, First Year, UA146.001.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Pathophysiology Pulmonary Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus, 1994, First Year, UA146.001.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Pharcology Syllabus Unit B Section I, 1997, UA146.001.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Pharcology Syllabus Unit B Section II, 1998, UA146.001.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II, 1997, UA146.001.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Physical Diagnosis Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Pulmonary System Pathology Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Renal System Pathology Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Reproductive System Pathology Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Reproductive System Pathology Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 2000, First Year, UA146.001.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Cardiovascular System Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Cell, Tissue and Organ Biology Syllabus Part I, 2000, First Year, UA146.001.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Class of 2000 First year Fall Semester, 2000, First Year, UA146.001.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Endocrine Pathology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - Pathology of the Gastrointestinal Tract Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - Pathology Reproductive System Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus Part I, 1996, UA146.001.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Pulmonary Pathology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - Renal Pathology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Cell, Tissue and Biology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Endocrine Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Epidemiology and Biostatistics Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - GI Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - History of Medicine, 1994, UA146.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 1994, First Year, UA146.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology Cardiovascular Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology Pulmonary Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology Renal Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Patient Doctor Society, 1994, UA146.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Pulmonary Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Renal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Supplement Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Class of 2000 Second Year Spring Semester Unites C, D, & E, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Infectious Diseases Syllabus Part I, 1997, UA146.001.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Infectious Diseases Syllabus Part II, 1997, UA146.001.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Infectious Diseases Syllabus Part III, 1997, UA146.001.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manual, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 1996, First Year, UA146.001.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology Endocrine Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology GI Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Pathophysiology Reproductive Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus Part II, 1996, UA146.001.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - principles and Practice of Medicine (PPM) PPM II Care of the Elderly Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Pulmonary System Pathology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - The Breast and Pelvic Examination Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Ethics in Medicine Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Hematology Syllabus, 1998, First Year, UA146.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Infectious Disease Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Introduction to Clinical Skills Syllabus, UA146.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Head- Neck Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Abdomen Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Pelvis and Perineum Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Thorax Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 2000, UA146.001.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part II, 1998, UA146.001.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Musculoskeletal System Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Nutrition Handout Nutrition During Pregnancy and Lactation, 1996, UA146.001.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Nutrition Handout Resources for the Micronutrient Deficiencies/Clinical Evaluation: B12, 1996, UA146.001.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Nutrition Handout Resources for the Micronutrient Deficiencies/Clinical Evaluation: Iron, 1996, UA146.001.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Slides from 8/22/96 Lecture, 1999, UA146.001.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section I Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Preclinical Selective Program Catalog, 1994, UA146.001.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 1996, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Cardiovascular System Pathology Syllabus, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1999 Second Year Fall Semester, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Class of 2000 Second Year Fall Semester, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Endocrine System Pathology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Gastrointestinal Pathology Syllabus, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - History of Medicine Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 1999, UA146.001.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00032 (Box 12)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manuel, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00033 (Box 12)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00034 (Box 12)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 2000, Second Year, UA146.001.012.00035 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II, 1999, UA146.001.012.00036 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II, 1999, UA146.001.012.00037 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit A Section II, 2000, UA146.001.012.00038 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section I, 2000, UA146.001.012.00039 (Box 12)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section II, 2000, UA146.001.012.00040 (Box 12)
  - Preclinical Selective Program Catalog, 1996, UA146.001.012.00041 (Box 12)
  - Renal System Pathology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.012.00042 (Box 12)
  - Reproductive System Pathology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.012.00043 (Box 12)
  - Endocrine System Pathology Syllabus, 2003, UA146.001.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Epidemiology and Biostatistics Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 1996, First Year, UA146.001.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Medical Genetics Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Extremities Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Pathophysiology Endocrine Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Pathophysiology Reproductive Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Preclinical Selective Program Catalog, 1996, UA146.001.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine Nutrition and Medicine Basic Nutrition Block Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Cardiovascular System Pathology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Hematology Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Human Growth and Development Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Medical Clinical Anatomy Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Medical Clinical Anatomy Syllabus, 2004, UA146.001.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Medical Genetics Syllabus, 2004, UA146.001.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part I, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part II, 2004, UA146.001.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Pathophysiology- Cardiovascular and Infectious Disease, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Pathophysiology- Gastrointestinal Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Pathophysiology- Pulmonary/Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Pathophysiology- Renal/Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Introduction to Clinical Medicine and Clinical Encounter Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - Pulmonary System Pathology Syllabus, 2003, UA146.001.013.00025 (Box 13)
  - Systemic Pathology Gastrointestinal Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - Systemic Pathology Renal System Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00027 (Box 13)
  - Systemic Pathology Reproductive Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - Cell, Tissue, and Organ Biology Syllabus Part I, 1999, First Year, UA146.001.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Infectious Diseases Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Introduction to Clinical Skills Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Introduction to Clinical Skills Syllabus, UA146.001.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Pelvis and Perineum Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 1995, First Year, UA146.001.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Behavioral Science and Primary Care Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Behavioral Science Part II Health and Illness during the life cycle: human growth and development syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Biochemistry Conferences, 1999, First Year, UA146.001.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1997 Second Year Spring Semester, 1997, Second Year, UA146.001.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Endocrine Metabolic Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Epidemiology and Biostatistics Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Ethics in Medicine Syllabus, 1993, UA146.001.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 1995, First Year, UA146.001.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Abdomen Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Extremities Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Head and Neck Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Head and Neck Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Pelvis and Perineum Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Thorax Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 1999, UA146.001.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part I, 1997, UA146.001.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part II, 1997, UA146.001.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 1997, UA146.001.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Patient Doctor Society Introduction to Family Medicine Block Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Patient Doctor Society Introductory Block, 1995, UA146.001.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Patient Doctor Society Perspectives of Medicine Block Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Pharmachology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Pharmachology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II, 1999, UA146.001.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section I, 1998, UA146.001.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section I, 1998, UA146.001.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section I, 1998, UA146.001.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Unit B Section II, 1998, UA146.001.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Pulmonary Pathology Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Pulmonary Pathphysiology Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.014.00039 (Box 14)
  - Renal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1995, UA146.001.014.00041 (Box 14)
  - Hematology Syllabus, 1997, First Year, UA146.001.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Behavioral Science and Primary Care Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1996, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Cardiovascular System Pathology Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Cardiovascular System Syllabus, 1996, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Class of 1999 Second Year Spring Semester, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Endocrine Pathology Syllabus, 1994, UA146.001.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Endocrine System Pathology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Gastrointestinal Pathology Syllabus, 1999, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - GI Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - GI Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Introduction to Clinical Skills Syllabus, UA146.001.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Issues in Community and Family Health Syllabus, 1993, UA146.001.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Issues in Community and Family Health Syllabus Part III, 1993, UA146.001.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Pelvis and Perineum Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 1999, UA146.001.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 1999, UA146.001.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory Part I, 1997, UA146.001.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1996, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 1996, Second Year, UA146.001.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Pathophysiology Endocrine Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Pathophysiology Pulmonary Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Pathophysiology Pulmonary Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Pathophysiology Renal Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Pathophysiology Reproductive Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 1996, UA146.001.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Section II Part I, 1999, UA146.001.015.00029 (Box 15)